najah.edu 2009-10-17

# Privacy Policy : An-Najah National University : Palestine

HomePrivacy Policy

* * *

* * *

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at najah.edu. 

**The information we collect **

In some instances you can use information, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services. 

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit  many of our web pages such as the type  of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, internet explorer ) the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Microsoft windows or Mac OS ) and the domain name of your internet service provider. 

**How we use the information **

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our publications, conferences and other services to respond to your inquiries about our information, and to offer you other publications conference invitations or service that we believe may be of interest to you 

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as when we make changes to our subscriber agreements to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter or to contact you about your account with us. 

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalise your internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyse site usage, as well as to offer you programs. 

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order we also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. In addition, we may transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another institution. 

Agents and contractors of An-Najah National University who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for An-Najah. 

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice. 

We may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to convey to you information or services that may be of interest to you. 

**Our Commitment to Security **

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. 

**How you can Access or Correct Information **

For instructions on how you can access the personally identifiable information that our site has collected about you online, or how to correct factual errors in such information m please contact us. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

If you have any questions or concerns about an-najah online policy for this site or its implementation contact us. [pr@najah.edu](mailto:pr@najah.edu)

From time to time, we may update this privacy notice. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. 

Number of Views 5848
